posterous.com 2010-11-21

# Privacy Policy - Posterous - The place to post everything. Just email us. Post and share from anywhere..

Hey, thanks for coming. Would you mind signing in? 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

#### The Information We Collect

Any information gathered by Posterous is used to customize the Posterous experience, and is not shared or sold to any third parties, except as expressly provided for in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.

Posterous reserves the right to view private sites and private posts for the purposes of fixing issues, and to look for copyrighted or other inappriate material. This will only be done as necessary and these posts will never be shared by anyone else. 

#### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We believe in protecting your information just as we would want our information protected.

In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Posterous will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

#### Notifications

It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to our users via e-mail notice, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on the Posterous website, as determined by us in our sole discretion. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Posterous reserves the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to our users.

#### Child Protection

We do not offer services to, or target, persons under the age of 13. In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we will purge any information we receive from people we believe to be children under 13 from our database and cancel the corresponding accounts.

#### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in and "Editing" your account. Your password is needed to edit this information, even if you are already logged in. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. The main form of identity management is your e-mail address. Please always use a valid and up-to-date e-mail address.

#### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us e-mail at [help@posterous.com](mailto:help@posterous.com).
